Let's gather 'round the campfire, and sing our campfire song
Our C-A-M-P-F-I-R-E S-O-N-G song
And if you don't think that we can sing it faster then you're wrong
But it'll help if you just sing along
Bum，bum，buuum... INAF!!
C-A-M-P-F-I-R-E S-O-N-G song
And if you don't think that we can sing it faster then you're wrong
But it'll help if you just sing along
sing~~ C-A-M-P-F-I-R-E S-O-N-G song
C-A-M-P-F-I-R-E S-O-N-G song
And if you don't think that we can sing it faster then you're wrong
But it'll help if you just sing along
C-A-M-P-F-I-R-E S-O-N-G song
And I wanna thank you all for singing with me today that's the song
I wanna say thank you for singing along
one more time
C-A-M-P-F-I-R-E S-O-N-G song
And if you don’t think that you can sing it faster then you’re wrong
and it helped that you sang it along
nice~  nice job~~ %%%